godfather_deck = Deck.create(subject: "The Godfather")
card_one = Card.create(question: "Diane Keaton played the character 'Connie' in The Godfather", answer: "false", deck_id: 1, deck: godfather_deck)
card_two = Card.create(question: "A dead fish was sent as a message to the Corleone household telling them that Luca Brasi was dead", answer: "true", deck_id: 1, deck: godfather_deck)
card_three = Card.create(question: "Johnny Fontaine is a famous guitar player in The Godfather", answer: "false", deck_id: 1, deck: godfather_deck)
card_four = Card.create(question: "Vito Corleone died on the sidewalk after being shot", answer: "false", deck_id: 1, deck: godfather_deck)
card_five = Card.create(question: "The gun that Michael used to kill Sollozzo was hidden under a sink", answer: "false", deck_id: 1, deck: godfather_deck)
card_six = Card.create(question: "Michael's first wife was named Apollonia", answer: "true", deck_id: 1, deck: godfather_deck)
card_seven = Card.create(question: "'Hitting the Mattresses' means ducking from gunfire", answer: "false", deck_id: 1, deck: godfather_deck)
card_seven = Card.create(question: "Tattaglia is the name of one of the other five families in New York", answer: "true", deck_id: 1, deck: godfather_deck)
card_eight = Card.create(question: "Clemenza turns out to be a traitor towards the Corleone family", answer: "false", deck_id: 1, deck: godfather_deck)
card_nine = Card.create(question: "Spaghetti was Sollozzo's last meal", answer: "false", deck_id: 1, deck: godfather_deck)
